
Description

iAbidan Dictionary is an English to Myanmar offline dictionary, can work without internet connection. This dictionary provides dictionary and synonyms results for your iPhone, iPad and iPod devices. And also provides voice, bookmarks and share features. To using this dictionary you no need to pay any charges. ENJOY!!



Eng-Myan Dictionary
English to Myanmar Dictionary

Eng-Myan Dictionary is an English to Myanmar offline dictionary. This dictionary provides dictionary and synonyms results, and also provides voice, bookmarks, recents features. This dictionary contain few sample pictures for some definitions. To using this dictionary you no need to pay any charges.

- 21984 words definitions
- Images - 933
